So hey guys welcome back to my new video.
Here ICICI LBA has published its Q4 results.
Here you will see that on
15th April 2025, we will go directly
to their data and understand the data and
make a comparison.  And before reading the data, let me
tell you here that
they have announced to give a dividend of ₹7.
So here you will
also get ₹7 dividend per equity share.
Here you will see that all the figures are given in rupees in
lakhs.  So we will
understand this by converting it into crores.  First of all let us talk about
total income i.e. total revenue.
So if we look here, it was 5165
in quarter four of 2024.
In this current quarter, you will
see that 5851 crores are visible here.
And if we talk about the last quarter three, it was
5882 crores.  So friends, if we
talk about percentage here, then on yearly
basis, a jump of
13% is being seen here.  Here it has increased from 5165 to 5851, hence a
jump of 13% is being seen.   If we
compare it with the previous quarter three, then
here a slight decline of
0.53 is seen in their revenue.
Let us now talk about the total expenses of the company
i.e. what are the total expenses.
So here
we will see in the total expense section.
463 crores in the fourth quarter of the previous year 2024, which has
increased to Rs. 463 crores in this quarter.
Here you will see
5435 crores and if we talk about the last quarter three, it will be
5197 crores.  So there is a slight decline on a yearly basis
and also a little bit from quarter three here, I'd like to
apologize.  There is an
increase here on an annual basis
and
there is a slight increase
in their expenses since the last quarter three also.  Let us now talk about the profit of the company
i.e. profit after
tax.  So here we will see profit
and loss after tax i.e. PAT.  So
in the quarter four of 2024, it was 519 crores, here a
slight decline is being seen to
509 crores in the current quarter and if we
talk about the last quarter three, then here it has
decreased significantly from 724 to 509.
So friends, here you will see that on year on
year basis there is a decline of about 2%
in their profit and if we
compare it with the last quarter three, then here a
decline of about 30% is visible
in their profit.  Let us now talk about their
earnings per share.  Here we will
look at earnings per shares.
In the fourth quarter of 2024, it was
₹1.5 and in this quarter there is a little
decline to
₹10.29 and in the third quarter of the previous year it was
₹14.63, so here there is a decline on year on year basis as well
and a
much bigger decline is being seen
in their EPS since the fourth quarter of the previous year.  So friends, this
was the result of ICICI LBT which cannot be called very good
and
its performance here is seen to be quite slow as compared to market expectations.
Decline is also visible in their revenue profit and EPS.   It is
visible.  So friends, I hope
you liked the video.
Please like it.  If this is your first time on the channel, then I will
subscribe to the channel to see such quality content.  See you
in the next video.  Thank you.